

KB Mohan Full stack developer

O Bengaluru, Karnataka

☑ mohan.kb5473@gmail.com

% +91-7259615473

SOCIAL

in @Mohankumara-k-b

f @manu.kb3

@ @manu.kmh

PROFILE

I am a responsible and dedicated individual who is always eager to learn new things. I have successfully completed various complex projects in the past and have over 9+ years of experience in the software development field, with numerous achievements to my credit

EDUCATION

Degree

B.E-EC, UVCE Bengaluru

2010-2014

PUC/12th

PCMB, GJC Kadur

2008-2010

SKILLS

Pega PRPCSQL

Pega RPA

• HTML, CSS, JS, Jquery

JAVA

EXPERIENCE

Senior Manager

2021 - Present | Morgan Stanley

Working as an LSA on multiple projects, where responsible for gathering requirements, designing applications, and setting up environments.

Additionally, Part of the Pega COE team, where we identified reusable and repeatable functionalities and created frameworks/components for them.

System Architect II

2017 - 2021 | Pegasystems

Worked as a consultant at Pega, where provided expert services to clients for building applications in Pega. Also involved in the development of Pega offline mobile applications and successfully deployed several applications using Pega PRPC and Pega RPA tools.

Software Engineering Analyst

2014 - 2017 | Accenture

Served as a proficient Full Stack Developer, autonomously integrating DevOps practices into the application, and actively contributed to the architecture team.

CERTIFICATION

Pega CSS & CSSA

Pega PRPC certification on Pega both 7.X and 8.X version

Pega RPA

Pega Robotic Automation certification

Best Individual Contributor Award-2022

Morgan Stanley Yearly Award

PAVE Award

Pega Award for Excellence

ACE Award

Accenture Award for Excellence

REFERENCES

Vice Presidence | Morgan Stanley

Divya Sridhar

Phone: +1 732-688-5138

Email: divya.sridhar@morganstanley.com

Director | Pegasystems

Suraj Victor

Phone: +91 984-508-0010 Email: suraj.victor@in.pega.com

LANGUAGES

• Kannada • English • Telugu • Hindi • Tamil

INTERESTS

